Andrew Johnson



andrew.k.johnson228@gmail.com



303-210-4112



linkedin.com/in/andrew-johnson-24aaa223a



https://github.com/Johnson2017-stack

Summary

Professional Profile

In high school I took a web design class for HTML and CSS, In this course we had to find clients to build web sites for, We had a list and had to choose three out of the 20 clients on the list, of those three we had to contact them via Email and get a general idea of what kind of web cite they wanted for their business. Once we got the general idea we made a rough draft of their web site and sent it back to them, they critiqued us on what needed to be fixed or how we could make the web site better for their business.

I have tried to pursue my BS degree in computer science several times over the last two years, unfortunately I was working hurricane relief and worked around 80 hours a week and could not keep up with classes. I am now in a place in life that I can finally pursue my full degree as well as get back into the tech industry. As of right now I am taking classes at SkillSpire for Full Stack MERN software development. When I am finished with this course, I will start pursuing my AA in Computer science. I believe I am a good fit for your company because of my hard work ethic, my willingness to learn and my dedication to you and the team I may be working with.

Experience



Supply Chain Supervisor

Target Logistics Management LLC Jan 2011 - Jan 2012 (1 year 1 month)



Plant Operator 3

HALLIBURTON ENERGY SERVICES

Jan 2012 - Jan 2013 (1 year 1 month)



Lead Technician

Interstate Restoration Jan 2013 - Jan 2014 (1 year 1 month)



🖶 Water Technician

Palace Construction Inc. Jan 2014 - Jan 2015 (1 year 1 month)



Construction Foreman

Palace Construction Inc. Jan 2015 - Jan 2016 (1 year 1 month) superintendent in training, palace construction

Lead Technician

Interstate Restoration

Jan 2016 - Jan 2018 (2 years 1 month)

Water Technician

BAXTER CONSTRUCTION LLC

Jan 2021 - Jan 2023 (2 years 1 month)

Education



SkillSpire

full stack MERN software Development, Computer Science 2023 - 2023

certification

Tumwater High School

High School Diploma

The Art Institutes

Physical Classes



Colorado Technical Institute

BS, computer science

Skills

css • financial • html • javascript • lotus notes • management • software development • supervisory skills · web site production